[opening theme music playing]
SWEET HUNGER
"I can see that you're big and strong."
"But you wouldn't eat me, would you?"
Is that too high and mighty?
"I can see that you're big and strong...
but... you wouldn't eat me, would you?"
Just terrible! Now I sound too scared.
This girl is supposed to trust
her carnivore friend, not fear them.
But wait, does trust have
a different sound than friendship?
How about...
"Hang on, you wouldn't eat me, would you?"
[groans] Still wrong!
[sighs]
I WANT TO ASK YOU SOMETHING,
CAN WE MEET THIS AFTERNOON?
[Juno]
"I can see that you're big and strong,
but you wouldn't eat me, would you?"
Oh...
- "But... you wouldn't eat me, would you?"
- What the...
- What are you doing, Juno?
- [Juno] What?
Oh! No, this is, uh, for drama club.
[Lemur] I'm glad you were just acting.
You don't want to overdo it.
Juno's always worrying
about something.
- Oh, you've put on some weight.
- Really? No!
I guess you eat
when you're stressed out?
[laughs] Well, I say eat up.
Do what you want.
You're a senior, not a freshman.
- You heard the news?
- What?
I felt like something big was coming,
but I didn't expect this.
Well, he's a Beastar candidate,
so why not?
Uh, hold on. What are you talking about?
What? You don't know?
Take a look.
MAYOR, ZOOLYMPIC BID...
"LOUIS APPOINTED AS AMBASSADOR"
- They named him Zoolympic Ambassador!
- That makes him a celebrity now, right?
Well, was he ever really "normal"
like the rest of us?
I know what you mean.
[chuckles nervously]
Okay. I just need to calm down.
He's going to still have time for me.
Right? Yeah, I'm sure.
- [phone beeps]
- Huh?
[frustrated sigh]
Sorry for the wait, guys.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Oh.
Hey...
Roar! Do you like my lion?
[laughs]
- [Haru] Here you go.
- Thank you!
[mother] That was sweet of you
to bring that back.
- [Haru] Do you like lions?
- Mm-hm!
I'm going to be a lion when I grow up.
- Is that so? A lion?
- [donkey foal laughs]
Because they're cute!
- [shop clerk] Hey, Haru!
- Huh?
- Service table six.
- [Haru] Yeah, on it.
- Careful with this.
- Right.
[grunts softly]
I have your order right he-- Whoa!
Juno?
Oh, Haru!
[chuckles nervously]
Wha...
Uh, did you eat all of those?
Huh? No, of course not!
All right, I did!
[frustrated sigh]
Are you okay?
How about I...
just make some room on the table here.
- [Juno exclaims nervously]
- Huh?
Haru, I need a friend right now.
So you're saying, this guy you like,
he has a fiancée?
Unfortunately.
Well, what else can you tell me about him?
He was a senior at my school.
I really wanted to tell him
about my performance.
Oh, he's in the theatre?
He graduated back in the spring,
so he's not around anymore.
You don't see him much?
I mustered up the courage to contact him,
but then this!
What kind of message is that?
I HAVE PLANS WITH MY FIANCÉE TODAY. SORRY.
Look at what he wrote me!
[Haru] It's Louis?
[Juno] Does it get any ruder?
Uhh... You're right, that's pretty cold.
That's what I'm saying!
Who gets someone's hopes up
just to let them down?
[Haru] What's gotten into him?
If this were me, I could handle it.
But Juno's fur isn't thick enough
for these games.
Wait a minute.
Why do she and I
have the same taste in boys?
Ah, I wonder if he was dating
someone else at school.
Huh? Oh, uh-- That'd be silly.
Well, uh, probably not.
If he's engaged, that'd be weird.
Hm. Arranged relationships
seem so cold to me.
You're not allowed to just fall in love.
What made you fall for him?
Do you remember?
[chuckles]
In public, he's always so put together.
But in reality...
[Haru] He puts up a front,
but he can be very vulnerable.
That drew me to him, too.
He's so cute when he's vulnerable!
Huh?
If you boss him around a little,
he acts put out,
but I can tell he likes it.
- Also--
- Are you serious?
- I mean, is he really like that?
- Oh, yeah.
He's all stoic and intellectual,
but then he's flustered
just like a little kid.
- [chuckles]
- Wow. Imagine that.
I know, it's crazy!
I've never met anyone like that before.
I mean something to him.
Or at least that's what my heart tells me.
But what do I know?
[Haru] Oh, come on.
Haru, what if he's scared
I might try to eat him
and doesn't want to be around me?
I forgot to mention he's an herbivore.
I mean, you can relate, right?
Do you ever have the same thoughts
about Legoshi?
Maybe the safer choice for him
is his red deer fiancée.
You think that could be why
he chooses her over me?
[Haru] Well, uh, who really knows...
I can't help it!
There's something inside me
that can't quit him!
He's one of a kind!
He's got this aura,
he's always standing in the right light.
- Oh, I could eat him up he's so cute.
- [Haru] Hm?
Oh, uh, not like that, of course.
That's just a saying.
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
[crying]
[Haru] I get it.
Poor Juno.
She doesn't love Louis
because he's an herbivore.
She just loves Louis,
who happens to be an herbivore.
In the end, love is just love.
That, I understand.
I know your heart.
And I know you would never eat him.
Well, yeah...
[Haru] What was that?
- Just what you said.
- [Haru] Huh?
That's the way to say it.
When you told me
you know I'd never eat him.
Like you're being reassuring.
- [shop clerk] Haru!
- [Haru] Oh, be right there!
- Back to work.
- I appreciate it.
Thank you for listening.
Bye.
All right, then.
[heavy metal music playing]
[tires screeching]
Your idea of "classical" music
is a little strange.
Well, don't you sound just like my father.
You still don't know anything about me
do you, Louis?
Try this on for size.
This music makes me feel like
everything else doesn't matter.
I know you've had a lot on your plate,
so I appreciate you
making some time for me.
- What'd you say?
- [music stops]
Just that it seems
like you need a little break.
You look tired.
[reporter 1] ...as the official ambassador
for the upcoming Zoolympic bid.
[clicks]
I would've thought
you liked all this publicity.
I never would've guessed
you'd shy from it.
Well, look at that.
Seems like you don't know me
very well either.
Doesn't seem like a problem to me.
We have plenty of time
to get to know each other.
[scoffs] Hmm.
[Azuki] On a clear day,
you can see all these
beautiful sparkles on the sea.
- [Louis] The garden is quite lovely.
- [Azuki] That tree there...
[chuckles] My father planted the seeds
the same day I was born.
When we welcome our child into the world,
we should plant a tree.
[butler] Pardon the interruption.
[Azuki] This is from Father.
He wanted to congratulate you
on your ambassadorship.
It's quite an honor.
Please enjoy.
[chuckles softly]
[Azuki] A toast, to my future husband.
- I'm so proud of you.
- [Louis] Thank you.
I have a gift for you as well.
Blinds down.
Because of your appointment,
you'll be in the spotlight
quite a bit more.
As your wife, it's only right
that I help you maintain your appearance.
Sesame oil.
With scents of patchouli, moss,
and bay leaf. Calming, isn't it?
Uh... [chuckles softly]
Uh. Hang on a minute, I'm not sure...
Come on, don't be shy.
[Louis] Azuki...
[Azuki laughs] You're in good hands.
- Try to relax.
- [Louis sighs]
Mmm. Splendid antlers...
[Louis] These aren't actually
my real antlers.
They're fake, just until mine grow back.
That doesn't matter to me.
Whenever you're seen in public,
fake or real, these antlers are yours.
Which means they should be
big and beautiful.
Wouldn't you agree?
- Even if they're not actually my own?
- [Azuki] Yes.
Even if they're artificial,
they'll become real over time.
It just takes patience.
There's no guarantee of that.
[Azuki] That's fine too.
It's about perception.
How you're viewed
while in the spotlight is important.
- [Louis] Well, that's enough.
- Speaking of important,
the city's cleanup efforts...
Seems to be on everyone's mind lately.
What?
If we end up winning the Zoolympic bid,
there are pockets of the city we'd rather
not show the rest of the world.
I guess...
Certain elements
will need to be cleaned up.
For example, the Carnivore District.
Wha--
The Black Market, is that what you mean?
I heard about some unsavory elements
fighting over something around there.
So Father was saying that
they're going to clean it all up.
This is the first I've heard
of something like that.
What a shame. I'm looking forward to it.
[Louis] I should get going soon.
[Azuki] Are you sure?
The sea is beautiful at sunrise.
You want to watch it with me?
MADARA-GUMI
[Miso] Out of the way! Move it!
Madara-Gumi coming through!
[man 1] It's the Madara-Gumi!
Clear the way, clear out!
- [man 2] Oh, crap, run!
- [man 3] Not again.
[woman] Oh, my goodness!
Go back home.
[growls]
Hey, old man. How's business?
Good, thank you.
Here you are, this month's tribute.
[Miso] Ooh. [laughs]
Yeah, very nice. You're in good hands.
We'll keep an eye on your shop here
and make sure it's safe. [laughs]
Aah! [groans]
What the hell is this? Move it!
[man 4] The hell are you doing?
[Ten] If your uncultured brain
can handle it,
- I have a free life lesson.
- [Miso] Shut it!
Fine stilettos like these
are made for walking the red carpet.
[Miso] Cut the crap!
[Ten] If you don't watch yourself,
I'll soak a carpet red with your blood.
[Miso] Is that so?
You're getting pretty cocky there,
aren't you, Ten?
[laughs] Can you blame me?
You're looking at what
the Black Market needs right now.
- A helping hand. The Inari-Gumi.
- [woman 1] You know that's right.
The streets will always belong
to the Madara-Gumi.
- Right!
- Get this tacky junk out of here.
With pleasure, if you can take me down.
Ha! Little girl, big words.
- [woman] Watch out!
- [grunts]
Looks like it's playtime.
And I just paid this stand off.
[man] Jeez, do we have to do this
every day?
[man 2] I miss the days when Shishi-Gumi
had that deer for a boss.
What?
That's unreal. Who has the money for that?
- [Jimma grunts]
- [thwacking]
You bastard!
[Free] You know not to screw with us!
Everybody gets protection,
- 'cause everybody always pays!
- [Jimma] Pay up!
Where's that "protection"
when the Inari-Gumi or the Madara-Gumi
destroy my shop?
Then I'd have no problem.
[Victor] You've got a dirty mouth.
[turtle groans]
You know it's the truth!
I'm still waiting till
we get any kind of real protection.
What?
Come on, we never even sat down
and signed a contract.
You guys are just holed up
in your hideout,
abandoned by the deer
and by your mixed boss too.
Gotta say, it's pretty embarrassing.
So, what you're sayin' is,
you'd like trip to the bottom of the sea?
Oh.
- All right. Okay, I'll pay.
- Huh?
You win! I'll pay up. I'll give you extra!
Mercy! Please show mercy!
[laughs]
Now you're talking.
That's what I like to hear.
- [footsteps approaching]
- Huh?
[gasps]
What the hell?
[sighs] I'm exhausted.
As a lone herbivore
walking through the Black Market,
I thought it would be safer
if I had a price tag.
- But it just made me stand out more.
- No surprise there.
[Jimma] As usual, you're totally fierce.
- [Free] So then...
- [Louis] Hm?
Uh... So does your stunt in the Black Market
mean that you're returning
to lead the Shishi-Gumi?
[all exclaim]
No. You know I can't do that.
I turned that down.
- [all sigh wearily]
- [Victor] What're you doin' to us?
- [Miguel] Getting our hopes up!
- [Victor sighs]
I've got some news you need to hear.
I wanted to make sure
you got the heads-up.
The city is going to start
cleaning up the Black Market.
"Cleaning up"?
I don't know specifically
how it's going to work,
but I figured it was something important
you needed to know.
You came all the way here
just to tell us this?
Uh, yeah.
And now that I have, see ya.
- [Jimma] Uh, hang on, where's the fire?
- [Free] Hold on a minute!
You're already here,
might as well hang a bit.
I bet you're starving! Right?
We'll make something nice!
[sniffing]
You know,
you've got kind of a different smell.
- [Dolph] Yeah, I thought the same thing.
- [sighs]
I've been through a lot lately.
- [Agata] I bet it's about a woman.
- Aw, guys. Come on.
You guys have to know
that you really stink.
You're bathing, right?
We do get wet from all the tears
from the broken hearts,
- but never under a shower.
- Hey!
- [all laughing]
- Come on, stop it.
You think I wanna be a stinky lion
like you guys?
What's wrong with me?
I can't believe the smell of this pride
is actually comforting.
[Victor] Come on, he came all this way,
and we don't have a single thing
we can make for Louis?
Eh, it's not like we even know
what "gourmet" means.
Well, we have this meat!
Idiot!
Find something for herbivores.
Oh!
[Miguel] What do you got?
[all] This is it!
Ta-da!
Apologies for the delay!
We present, the finest,
most premium melon,
prepared just for our friend Louis!
- [Agata shushing]
- Huh?
[shushes]
- [Victor] Hm?
- [Jimma] What?
Unbelievable...
We've got an herbivore layin' here
in a carnivore den.
And he's out like a light.
UDON BEBEBE
[guard] Oh, looks great!
[Legoshi sighs] Please enjoy.
Where's Haru?
I remember her saying
she was gonna be working today.
[sniff] Oh?
[sniffs] Haru's scent!
Uh, the smell is coming from here, but...
guess she's not here after all.
Huh? [sniffing]
That smell...
No way. It can't be.
[sniffing]
Melon!
[student 1] You see that?
Seems kind of shady...
Huh?
- [student 2] Should we report him?
- Oh, no...
- [Dom] Wait. Isn't that Legoshi?
- [Legoshi] Huh?
Hey! What's up, Dom?
[laughs]
It's fine. I know him from school.
- Ah.
- Oh.
Well, hi! I didn't know you went here.
Yeah, I'm studying art.
Can't believe I ran into you.
This is a nice surprise!
[Dom] Do you still keep in touch
with everyone from the drama club?
[Legoshi] Well,
I did drop by the club last month.
Everyone was hard at work.
You know, it's tough at the school,
separating carnivores and herbivores.
It's the same even for clubs, I hear.
So, have you been
in touch with them at all?
Well, I do chat with Kai every now
and then, I suppose.
- Kai, huh? Is he doin' all right?
- [laughs]
He said he thrives in adversity.
Seems like he's embraced becoming
a real part of the drama club
instead of just an "actor."
[Legoshi laughs]
Good on him!
Out there on the lawn,
what were you sniffing around for?
Huh?
Oh, uh... [chuckles nervously]
You don't have to say.
Oh, uh... Just taking in the scents.
Right now,
that's not the best look on campus.
There's been a lot unusual things
going on lately.
What do you mean by that?
[Dom exhales]
Like a professor falling to their death.
Or a student almost getting devoured.
Everyone's a bit on edge right now.
Wow, that sounds like a lot.
[Dom] It's not just here,
but it seems everywhere
is getting dangerous, don't ya think?
[Legoshi] Mm-hm.
You going to the Festival?
- [Legoshi] That's the plan.
- Cool, hope to see you there.
[Legoshi] Yeah. Take care!
[sighs]
[long sniff]
Here's the scent I picked up
when I showed up on campus.
So about Melon,
apparently he's called "Professor"
in polite society.
[Legoshi] This is it.
[exhales] Hmm.
Melon...
You're not getting away.
We're told that early this morning,
in this apartment right behind me...
BREAKING NEWS: BROWN BEAR SUSPECTED
IN DEVOURING INCIDENT ALSO FOUND MURDERED
...a female llama was devoured.
The brown bear
believed to have committed the crime
was also found dead at the scene.
This quiet street connecting
the Algama District and Center Street
is where we find our gruesome scene.
[closing theme song playing]